EXAMS = {
    "csir_net": "CSIR-NET",
    "nbhm": "NBHM",
    "gate": "GATE",
    "jam": "IIT JAM",
    "isi": "ISI",
    "cmi": "CMI"
}



PDF_LINKS = {
    "nbhm": {
        "combined": {
            "label": "Combined (2023–Present)",
            "years": {
                "2026": {
                    "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1XICMZfd3VNt94m5e71xbdjawY6IYUmAK&export=download",
                    "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1UXIbXwMXfdX5aBfUd1uz1q_xdB-Q8U0H&export=download"
                },
                "2025": {
                    "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1Chg3CckdgXld46Wv1JGMCqsgKj2eAQsf&export=download",
                    "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=14bPp_vo94hbGYwkbnROfMwt0qKIk6yKh&export=download"
                },
                "2024": {
                    "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1Ry8EuRvPZo5-4gIB9xhllRTWhv_g_OWc&export=download",
                    "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1z20g4QXDA_6-4xmdHNvWz9juKW6iA3jx&export=download"
                }
            }
        },

        "masters": {
            "label": "Master's (2005–2022)",
            "years": {
                "2019": {
                    "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1UUPL-Fa8gtGuiFDqw9oZk4hbdRWzLtzE&export=download",
                    "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=159th6h47uqhbAXu5B7ng2MpfADvQZYN8&export=download"
                },
                "2018": {
                    "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1pyVdNcVeIY_3jl4u1IcHzEdAS_UqH6s1&export=download",
                    "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1K6DWlMbK0bX_Sn6uu5s8B99kRvLe1lcO&export=download"
                },
                "2017": {
                    "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1kZlT-TjkvS6XwWNLUvYJNgwFvdf6MbpH&export=download",
                    "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1W-lxhi2sEB7VgQHB-kcTbN-ogCSEC6B6&export=download"
                },
                "2016": {
                    "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1e04-lnI1wUgcp1YQrC6W0WHW8aBfQp5F&export=download",
                    "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1I-JxJBPPqSzx8rkOjYmZEC3S2E8g9usx&export=download"
                },
                "2015": {
                   "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1zNHtWYKLRrEfGX4cCnKL3DmyMqUMimXu&export=download",
                   "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1EgftjugN74_pF1K7ZPytQbnfJCbIVu-B&export=download"
                },
                "2014": {
                   "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1ZpVUAbJnerrQZhB_SqhDdIc1DWPt3ljA&export=download",
                   "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=10XsKShoG6PTO3o6wQfq60dBphgapq15O&export=download"
                },
                "2013": {
                   "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1GjMTfh_KyCPM-yguXcxDGAIS24mdARQM&export=download",
                   "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1UpgJtBvSJxgQ8Fa9K1n5ihDXAIOBD8SM&export=download"
                },
                "2012": {
                   "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1Jszv3eVp-VcjgsCJzBcXY2D8avdAJliJ&export=download",
                   "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1m3Md5W2Ws5BTACNI8kUe4zEDdlCzirFw&export=download"
                },
                "2011": {
                   "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=14QZS4A-ewnDI3EoYKuoj8f4hNoWIt2ko&export=download",
                   "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1eY3pgfxWWiPwykDRbFmFEAF1sepFIhJ9&export=download"
                },
                "2010": {
                   "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1JWFc0f-fFBlve2-CNjXl3bTENuO4-arM&export=download",
                   "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1OCKblCc7XMcBLAUiOild6m9JCTPfmBXi&export=download"
                },
                "2009": {
                   "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1AKR6fsh6mR7kwQf6wI-4tBy6f74MrfAs&export=download",
                   "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1I_EC0VRPTaH6VjZ0k09c8XWt_nSA68t7&export=download"
                },
                "2008": {
                   "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1W0Hv2oKb7NU8L3Kx_z1EELO-ddz5Mu0e&export=download",
                   "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1jyQL_yXEZl7bbNLwuGG5aeWazVDsqrzW&export=download"
                },
                "2007": {
                   "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1ctVxO5VVymc-dEg3YebGxSJTeLszmCTA&export=download",
                   "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1v9pBMk6kdUOEHPC7omXh1oHqS6ThJjfm&export=download"
                },
                "2006": {
                   "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1FugwKFEqrn4s-6dkhaOJXkAWt5vsFQQP&export=download",
                   "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1MLG2BYRwsI87DW78jJb2HUaNVI6qiPNm&export=download"
                },
                "2005": {
                   "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=14fUWoVNEswgGTgABYXa1TXJbspjFvdaz&export=download",
                   "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1fCFxG5w6qcVQwcL0viOSTC8O1Og_uRan&export=download"
                }
            }
        },

        "doctoral": {
            "label": "Doctoral (2005–2022)",
            "years": {
                "2022": {
                    "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1LGQvl-7CutQzRPCSwyrLC1FsPHPKUceG&export=download",
                    "answer": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1dSh0BsKKqkE-o1u2O7WwxP4SurlRJkFo&export=download"
                }
            }
        }
    },

    "gate": {
        "2023": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1UXIbXwMXfdX5aBfUd1uz1q_xdB-Q8U0H&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1UXIbXwMXfdX5aBfUd1uz1q_xdB-Q8U0H&export=download"
        }
    },

    "jam": {
        "2025": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1INSpYBq7x5HPWLy7362mGZwOSI2ah0eu&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=16E2Hi5Qpn-hEQLUSQV6GCQpdnSTbIAbs&export=download"
        },
        "2024": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=13uZAZxLj-IQ0lPe8q-SpjkPWDp07EC57&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1-oCs2ilpUX7k5SBK574WH61trMSmzoAV&export=download"
        },
        "2023": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1NXRzCDJUDgmp1U_R2a5uFuQS5q-QTCyt&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1rd7hyJHah6ChjuctdOo-zqpLxDxp97vM&export=download"
        },
        "2022": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1Te2dhYJPuZKOEibig2FccfYONud_rsrk&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1-DcyIC6bU6A09Agq2eh6MJnXfU-z_cJL&export=download"
        },
        "2021": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1bP1ES5RQiPQqBRvElcwVt7QTHfAtCmlZ&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1NkCXE17b5DTC52SQVBKpZix1FXnOMm9m&export=download"
        },
        "2020": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1bf5ED34uaDvjPg5ZqoNyFdjPrFx-HwX_&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1GtVGmD6Qu0Ke7GPvEVRBDzkTaUEq--Gr&export=download"
        },

        "2019": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1PpcxsX5Jyu6R9p8fPXwtowDE8JK39Brk&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1sVXQN8Y_cFUrOFXk_cZFnLNSE2izarKn&export=download"
        },
        "2018": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1iH2A35YTjX8nF86nFCcA1OlBpCqB-87m&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1wrt9CvyQ6uZxDGtzCmJdxI9ox0JdIHB-&export=download"
        },
        "2017": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1oh0idUZEgZgRzKZOJCfynbeYjh9U40tf&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=18sgnedCZ0ONkCp8OX69em8ocb9hr4cYy&export=download"
        },
        "2016": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1Ae1UTflIz4X9JTqEw250yyMtqLKDxPfE&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=101-LApMrNoOJlaCUkJrU09tQ48WKpmSv&export=download"
        },
        "2015": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=16ndTJxxyG8GgnDhbyDO8G_Dx_jajlNBm&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1sNmnndhPvvucrAmHg0OlTfhhTACthlAH&export=download"
        },
        "2014": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=166nZ0Vg1RzVtGxF5Ad6uJa86egHEpO2F&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1jCkfbYrc8c6Fem8zfUkNl9l3lzhXipzH&export=download"
        }
    },

    "cmi": {
        "2025": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1knKk-tq2n0-1f8ufgj-hjSIsRQ0ZkAZ-&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1LA1mxaZnIVZAEsLV3cs2vpMAoKcnu8r9&export=download"
        },
        "2024": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1l2U3Fk5ybEQgkjIqZ0blQrDFsPX5s2Lj&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1q6MQrfpecO38xAWfr7jmQO3w7nZ7P-2D&export=download"
        },
        "2023": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1ixlMquZN6kSAl_ZFZOUoSmgurSxleZ0V&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1-6IhRoL7dMMPtXThqKpVoe3iBEyBlYQ_&export=download"
        },
        "2022": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=16tBOB6vGCIkbiLOnBKLRITUbIPcxC7b-&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1dJqfZFFAmYnTWNAhoOoYnLNNFqEJEIkP&export=download"
        },
        "2021": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1kZZb6_4R6xsb9xLHkdJ0lEQmm0-2oMOA&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1OFE2Qs7kMVEsV-2vVb0ucFmEHLQnMjiP&export=download"
        },
        "2020": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=12wyF9NESHFkcxNa1Epplb6WzstO3h6CB&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1AB1HhSmcyG3YVN1IwlLAl_r7PJPYAXv-&export=download"
        },

        "2019": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1IgPYkGJFc2Y4sauMFLpwb9SqoySEWge1&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1iJah_wukl-tFpy9kidqd_85Y5H6LA9d0&export=download"
        },
        "2018": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1QoKinddxfIXK66Cn5DUfUVcaLb7NkUne&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1B56ECkJ44i-hQpGqRKejoFarjIiLzbHf&export=download"
        },
        "2017": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1QyxHP2l6SViRu_1lp4-iDeJiZP8rmLs6&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=12BbqZ1SENaA6Otpug3778nQZu7KgejPn&export=download"
        },
        "2016": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1iNOiQ1oDkNuxMOkpTAOwNs5AcGGAwP79&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1cWY4JKvgAyOGvpQ1e6nov_IzEv2o4rdX&export=download"
        },
        "2015": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1XE_EPaeB80vP3ElWT6eNfsNh1ZhyUh05&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=14rqqxAmio6k4SuQMUplirUKn9iIp8K3J&export=download"
        },
        "2014": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=10yspO0iYHcABJ_pSumoAEYQDMUZMj133&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1_wzJRYNBGG0mUgaC3bbWnKe4uWYGegLZ&export=download"
        },
        "2013": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=10jsNPVljkCI5kt_BoawjJy65PW9wc_5I&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1Ph5ZHboTw0Be2C6RFIhu3OLs6MW2gNWx&export=download"
        },
        "2012": {
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1-MNQsgGxEefosezKkNy-spsSj0qxkkr-&export=download",
            "answer":   "https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1Dg45sMAQjmBUPX6faYH-vhgD1XaTFfv6&export=download"
        }
    }
}
